<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Tony's I/O</title><description>Thoughts, stories and ideas.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.6</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 15:41:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Network Visualization Project Log: 1</title><description>&lt;h5 id="intro"&gt;Intro&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am working on a network visualization web application. The purpose is to visual the network during cyber defense competitions. I am working with someone else. I am working on the server-side of the web app and setting up the testing infrastructure. My partner will be working on the&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/network-visualization/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3606c5f7-1839-45b3-99ee-ba05b5f29af3</guid><dc:creator>Tony Perez</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 15:40:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h5 id="intro"&gt;Intro&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am working on a network visualization web application. The purpose is to visual the network during cyber defense competitions. I am working with someone else. I am working on the server-side of the web app and setting up the testing infrastructure. My partner will be working on the client-side making the graphics using webGL. This project is suppose to be similar to Norse's &lt;a href="http://localhost:2368/network-visualization/map.ipviking.com"&gt;map.ipviking.com&lt;/a&gt; but for a local network and will show the different teams instead of continents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id="servicesused"&gt;Services Used:&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://qosient.com/argus"&gt;Argus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://nodejs.org"&gt;Node.js&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://socket.io"&gt;Socket.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The test environment will be on a CentOS 6.6 Virtual Machine. For now I will install everything on the same system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Argus is a network monitoring tool that will used to capture and produce the network flow in real time. Node.js will be used with socket.io to make a web socket that will feed the client(s) information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id="currentstatus"&gt;Current Status:&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Argus server and client is working.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working on getting a demo up that will show the argus client information on a web page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing the Node.js server that will output the data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any suggestion please contact me &lt;a href="mailto:pereztr@cs.sunyit.edu"&gt;@pereztr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>